<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Install KubeSphere Enterprise on KubeSphere Enterprise</title>
    <link>/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Install KubeSphere Enterprise on KubeSphere Enterprise</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>©2022 QingCloud, Inc. All rights reserved</copyright><atom:link href="/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Online Installation of Kubernetes and KubeSphere Enterprise</title>
      <link>/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/01-online-install-kubernetes-and-kubesphere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/01-online-install-kubernetes-and-kubesphere/</guid>
      <description>This section explains how to install Kubernetes and KubeSphere Enterprise in an Internet-accessible environment.
 The installation process will use the open-source tool KubeKey. For more information about KubeKey, please visit the GitHub KubeKey repository.
 Prerequisites   Prepare at least 1 Linux server as a cluster node. In a production environment, to ensure high availability of the cluster, it is recommended to prepare at least 5 Linux servers, with 3 servers as control plane nodes and 2 servers as worker nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activate KubeSphere Enterprise</title>
      <link>/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/03-activate-kse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/03-activate-kse/</guid>
      <description>After logging in to the KubeSphere Enterprise web console, you need to import a license to activate KubeSphere Enterprise and extensions to access all features.
     Note     If you installed KubeSphere Enterprise offline, please contact delivery specialists directly to get the license.
    Step 1: Purchase and obtain license For online installations of KubeSphere Enterprise, visit {ks_product-en} official website, click Contact Us, and inquire about purchasing method for KubeSphere Enterprise and extensions licenses via WeChat or Slack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Configure KubeSphere High Availability</title>
      <link>/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/04-configure-ks-high-availability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/04-configure-ks-high-availability/</guid>
      <description>This section explains how to configure high availability for KubeSphere.
     Note     KubeSphere high availability relies on high availability of Kubernetes control plane nodes, so ensure Kubernetes is deployed in HA mode first.
    1. High Availability Architecture Overview KubeSphere supports high availability deployment, which can be enabled via ha.enabled.
 In HA mode, Redis supports two deployment approaches:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Appendix: Advanced Configuration of KubeSphere Core</title>
      <link>/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/05-appendix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/v4.2.0/03-installation-and-upgrade/02-install-kubesphere/05-appendix/</guid>
      <description>KubeSphere Helm Chart Parameters Global Configuration     Name Description Value     global.imageRegistry
 Global Docker image registry
 registry.cn-beijing.aliyuncs.com
   global.tag
 Global Docker image tag
 &amp;#34;&amp;#34;
   global.imagePullSecrets
 Global Docker registry secret names as an array
 []
    Common Parameters     Name Description Value     nameOverride</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
